# OPEN TRIVIA DATABASE
question_data = [
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "easy",
        'question': "A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.",
        'correct_answer': "False",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "medium",
        'question': "111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321",
        'correct_answer': "True",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "easy",
        'question': "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.",
        'correct_answer': "False",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "hard",
        'question': "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;",
        'correct_answer': "False",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "hard",
        'question': "If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.",
        'correct_answer': "True",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "medium",
        'question': "Zero factorial is equal to zero. ",
        'correct_answer': "False",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "medium",
        'question': "A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.",
        'correct_answer': "True",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "hard",
        'question': "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.",
        'correct_answer': "True",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "medium",
        'question': "The set of all algebraic numbers is countable.",
        'correct_answer': "True",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        'category': "Science: Mathematics",
        'type': "boolean",
        'difficulty': "medium",
        'question': "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.",
        'correct_answer': "True",
        'incorrect_answers': [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
